[
   {
      "id":1,
      "question":"The rice dish ‘paella’ comes from what country?",
      "a":"Spain",
      "b":"Greece",
      "c":"Italy",
      "d":"Portugal",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":2,
      "question":"What is another name for maize?",
      "a":"Tomato",
      "b":"Corn",
      "c":"Pea",
      "d":"Chickpea",
      "answer":"b"
   },
   {
      "id":3,
      "question":"Deer meat is known by what name?",
      "a":"Veal",
      "b":"Bison",
      "c":"Venison",
      "d":"Pheasant",
      "answer":"c"
   },
   {
      "id":4,
      "question":"What product did Nintendo first start selling?",
      "a":"Video Games",
      "b":"Figurines",
      "c":"Gaming Consoles",
      "d":"Playing Cards",
      "answer":"d"
   },
   {
      "id":5,
      "question":"What is the best selling game in the world?",
      "a":"Pokemon",
      "b":"Wii Sports",
      "c":"Tetris",
      "d":"Minecraft",
      "answer":"d"
   },
   {
      "id":6,
      "question":"What is the highest-grossing arcade game of all time?",
      "a":"Pac-Man",
      "b":"Pong",
      "c":"Space-Invaders",
      "d":"Mortal Combat",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":7,
      "question":"How long should you wash your hands?",
      "a":"10 seconds",
      "b":"20 seconds",
      "c":"1 minute",
      "d":"5 seconds",
      "answer":"b"
   },
   {
      "id":8,
      "question":"What uses, on average, 26% of the water in a home?",
      "a":"Shower",
      "b":"Dishwasher",
      "c":"Toilet flushing",
      "d":"Bathing",
      "answer":"c"
   },
   {
      "id":9,
      "question":"What is the smallest form of bacteria called?",
      "a":"Spirilla",
      "b":"Bacilli",
      "c":"Vibrio",
      "d":"Cocci",
      "answer":"d"
   },
   {
      "id":10,
      "question":"Infants need about how many hours of sleep per day?",
      "a":"12 hours",
      "b":"10 hours",
      "c":"20 hours",
      "d":"16 hours",
      "answer":"d"
   },
   {
      "id":11,
      "question":"How long does a complete sleep cycle take?",
      "a":"100 minutes",
      "b":"3 hours",
      "c":"30 minutes",
      "d":"2 hours",
      "answer":"a"
   },
   {
      "id":12,
      "question":"Which of these will help promote better sleep?",
      "a":"Exercising 2h before bedtime",
      "b":"Reading or listening to music",
      "c":"Changing bedtimes",
      "d":"Having a late dinner",
      "answer":"b"
   }
]